{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "DECK 1",
      "description": "DECK 1 Description",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "DECK 2",
      "description": "DECK 2 description",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "DECK 3",
      "description": "DECK 3 description",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "DECK 4",
      "description": "DECK 4 description",
      "id": 4
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "DECK 1 - CARD A",
      "back": "DECK 1 - CARD A",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 1 - CARD B",
      "back": "DECK 1 - CARD B",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 1 - CARD C",
      "back": "DECK 1 - CARD C",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 2 - CARD A",
      "back": "DECK 2 - CARD A",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 2 - CARD B",
      "back": "DECK 2 - CARD B",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 2 - CARD C",
      "back": "DECK 2 - CARD C",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 3 - CARD A",
      "back": "DECK 3 - CARD A",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 3 - CARD B",
      "back": "DECK 3 - CARD B",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 3 - CARD C",
      "back": "DECK 3 - CARD C",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 4 - CARD A",
      "back": "DECK 4 - CARD A",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 4 - CARD B",
      "back": "DECK 4 - CARD B",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "DECK 4 - CARD C",
      "back": "DECK 4 - CARD C",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}